

CONTACT



(**៤))** +34 634 657 688



maolin1698@gmail.com



Sevilla, Spain



https://www.linkedin.com/in/m ao-lin-193064221/



DIGITAL SKILLS

Programming

- Python
- Java
- C
- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- ReactJS
- Django
- TailwindCSS
- Robot Framework
- Selenium
- Postman

Infrastructure as code

- Git
- SVN
- Jenkins
- Docker

Others

- JIRA
- JAMA
- SpiraTest
- MATLAB
- Wireshark
- VHDL

OTHER SKILLS

- · Agile methodologies such as scrums, sprints, etc.
- Proactive.
- Flexible.
- · Solution-oriented.
- · Good communication.

MAO LIN

Telecommunication engineer specialized in the field of electronics with near 5 year of experience in automated testing environments with CI/CD.

My ultimate passion is combining software and hardware and make it work in our day to day life.



WORKING EXPERIENCE

QA TEST ENGINEER

Woodswallow, Spain (Jan. 2022 - Nov. 2024)

- · Requirements traceability matrix analysis and coverage.
- · Test cases design, implementation and result analysis with Robot Framework.
- Development of Jenkins and GitLab environment for CI/CD pipelines
- Python back-end development of internal framework automated for testing.
- · Testing and handling of DLMS, IDIS, PRIME and ZigBee compliant devices.

QA TEST ENGINEER

AICIA, Spain (Jun. 2020 - Jan. 2022)

- · Test cases design, implementation and result analysis.
- Back-end development with Python.
- · Testing and handling of embedded systems.



EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in Telecommunication Engineering: Electronics

Universidad de Sevilla, Spain (2016 - 2021)

ISTQB® Certified Tester Foundation Level

Python Advanced Level Certification



LANGUAGES

- · Spanish (Native)
- English (Fluent, C1)
- · Italian (Basic)